<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>SSG Event RSS Feed</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/ssg-rss-feed.xml</link><description>Upcoming events in Sandy Springs</description><item><title>Sandy Spring Crafting Buddies</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-spring-crafting-buddies-8</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-spring-crafting-buddies-8</guid><description>Bring your current work in progress project, or materials to start a new project and come hang with us! Please feel free to bring any kind of craft (knitting, embroidery, cross stitching, drawing, painting, scrapbooking etc) and spend time working with other creatives!

Sandy Springs Crafting Buddies is free to attend! 

 

Sandy Springs Recreation and Parks inclusive community for people of all ages, abilities and skill sets to come together and share our common thread of passion for crafting. 
Join our Facebook group Sandy Springs Crafting Buddies. | Venue: Barfield Room</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-01/Crafting%20Buddies%20Web%20Asset%203840x2160-%20REV%201.00_2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Roswell Dance Theatre presents The Little Mermaid</title><link>https://citysprings.com/events/roswell-dance-theatre-presents-little-mermaid</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://citysprings.com/events/roswell-dance-theatre-presents-little-mermaid</guid><description>Join mermaid princess Ariel on her journey to land and life above the sea. Surrounded by her sea friends, she marvels at the treasures dropped by humans to the ocean floor and swims just to the edge of the water to glimpse the world of ships crossing overhead. After making a deal with the sea witch Ursula, Ariel has to overcome many challenges as she struggles to win the heart of Prince Eric and find the life she longs for in the sunshine. 

The entire family will delight as the cast of The Little Mermaid brings magic to the stage in this thrilling production. Join us at one of four enchanting performances in the beautiful Byers Theatre April 4-5.

Our youngest guests will enjoy two very special “Prince and Princess” Meet &amp;amp; Greet performances on Saturday, April 5. Come dressed in your favorite prince or princess costume and meet The Little Mermaid cast members! Dancers will sign autographs and pose for pictures one hour prior to curtain.  

Community groups welcome.  Contact the Box Office for group sales. 

Girl Scout troops - visit our page after purchasing tickets, to reserve a commemorative patch at the performance SpringBalletConcert.com. | Venue: Sandy Springs Performing Arts Center</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-01/d1fc2c39-de25-45b8-a777-68874d21d9db.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Wild Roots Nursery Native Plant Sale</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/wild-roots-nursery-native-plant-sale-0</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/wild-roots-nursery-native-plant-sale-0</guid><description>Spring is in the air and the garden is calling! Discover the best native plants for planting in your garden. Native plants are best conditioned to thrive, attract butterflies, bees and other pollinators. These plants enhance the local ecosystem and add beauty to every landscape. Wild Roots Native Nursery strives to make native plants widely available and has a great selection of plants for sun and shade! Come early for the best selection!

Trecia Neal and Stephanie Spencer, both master gardeners, are the owners of Wild Roots Native Nursery. The heart of Wild Roots Native Nursery is the determined commitment of its founders to fostering a revival of native gardening. Trecia and Stephanie, with dirt under their fingernails, want to educate communities about how native plants are best conditioned to thrive, attract pollinators and other wildlife, enhance the environment, and add natural beauty to every landscape. | Venue: Lost Corner Preserve</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/Wild%20Roots%20%20image.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Lantern Parade 2025</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/lantern</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/lantern</guid><description>The Lantern Parade is an evening filled with fantastical puppets and glowing lanterns! Families bring handcrafted lanterns, celebrate as the sun sets, then parade down to the Chattahoochee River!    

The Sandy Springs Lantern Parade will take place on Saturday, April 5, 2025. 

Learn more:  

🏮 Lantern Parade Website | Venue: Morgan Falls Overlook Park </description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/2025%20LP%20Website%20Asset%20REV%200.01.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Graham Nash</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/graham-nash</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/graham-nash</guid><description>Legendary artist Graham Nash, as a founding member of both the Hollies and Crosby, Stills and Nash, is a two-time Rock and Roll Hall of Fame inductee. An extraordinary GRAMMY Award® winning Renaissance artist – and self-described “simple man” – Nash was inducted twice into the Songwriters Hall of Fame, for his work with CSN and his work as a solo artist. Graham will be joined on stage by Todd Caldwell (keyboards and vocals), Adam Minkoff (bass, drums, guitars, and vocals), and Zach Djanikian (guitars, mandolin, drums, and vocals), performing favorites from across his sixty-year career. 

Ticket prices INCLUDE 7.75% sales tax. 

In addition to standard admission tickets, the following VIP Packages are also available for sale while limited supplies last.

VIP Package Details

SOUNDCHECK PACKAGE* (YELLOW) includes
• One premium reserved ticket
• Visit to pre-show Sound Check with Graham Nash
• One autographed tour poster
• One commemorative Graham Nash laminate
• One commemorative Graham Nash ticket
• Crowd-free merchandise shopping
• On-site VIP staff
* All VIP activities occur pre-show. Package details &amp;amp; timing subject to change.

PREMIUM PACKAGE* (RED) includes
• One premium reserved ticket
• One Graham Nash tour item
• One commemorative Graham Nash ticket
• On-site VIP staff
*Package details &amp;amp; timing subject to change. | Venue: Sandy Springs Performing Arts Center</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2024-10/1a7b0257-20d5-4a03-8b80-0f17df934652.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title> PBS Kids Story Time, April 2025 </title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/pbs-kids-story-time-april-2025</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/pbs-kids-story-time-april-2025</guid><description>Plan to join us the first Monday of each month for PBS Kids Story Time, with Georgia Public Broadcasting. Your little one (ages 2-6) will love all the things to do - storytelling, rhymes, crafts, and a PBS Kids show! Admission is free but registration is needed.

If you have specific accessibility needs, please contact Amanda Densmore at adensmore@gpb.org or call 404-685-2611. | Venue: Studio Theatre</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/PBS%20Kids%20Story%20Time%203840x2160%20smaller.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>City Green Live: Tonic </title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cgl-2025-tonic</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cgl-2025-tonic</guid><description>The story of Tonic revolves around the longstanding brotherhood shared among members Emerson Hart, Jeff Russo, and Dan Lavery. Since 1996, the GRAMMY®️ Award-nominated multi-platinum trio has consistently delivered anthemic and undeniable rock fashioned from eloquent songcraft, lyrical honesty, and unshakable melodies.


	Friday, April 11 

	
		4:00 p.m. - City Green opens 
		6:00 p.m. - Food Trucks open 
		7:30 p.m. - Opener
		8:30 p.m. - Tonic 
	
	
	Lawn seating is FREE and open to everyone.
	Reserved table seating may be available. 
	Food Trucks will be on site. 


 

City Green Live 

City Green Live features high-energy, nationally touring artists performing on the City Green, offering attendees a lively, outdoor music experience. 

🎸Getting Here + Know Before You Go

☀️Summer Concerts in Sandy Springs

 

Tonic 



Music always undoubtedly brings us closer together. The connection forged runs as deep as any family bond does. Similarly, the story of Tonic revolves around the longstanding, close brotherhood shared among members Emerson Hart [vocals, guitar], Jeff Russo [lead guitar], and Dan Lavery [bass]. Since 1996, the GRAMMY®️ Award-nominated multi-platinum trio has consistently delivered anthemic and undeniable rock fashioned from eloquent songcraft, lyrical honesty, and unshakable melodies. Along the way, they translated true experiences and real memories into a storied catalog that resounds as loudly today as it did over two decades ago.

“Sometimes, I’ll see somebody in the crowd who’s not more than twenty-years-old,” says Emerson. “This person will be singing a thought I had in 1995 right back to me: every word and every note. Realizing the power of that was a big moment for me. If there are people in the crowd and we’re playing together, that’s the magic of it. We still love it. There’s an understanding this is bigger than us.”

The songs continue to endure. To date, the band has landed six Top 10 singles, sold 4 million-plus records, and garnered a pair of GRAMMY®️ Award nominations. As the story goes, Emerson and Jeff linked up together in Los Angeles as Tonic during 1994, with Dan joining the group in 1996. Inspired after catching U2’s Joshua Tree Tour in his native New Jersey, Emerson went to L.A., where he and Jeff launched the group. Their full-length debut, Lemon Parade, not only went platinum, but it also yielded the “#1 Most-Played Rock Song of 1997” in the form of the lead single “If You Could Only See.” The band’s follow-up single, “You Wanted More,” served as the lead-off from the platinum Original Soundtrack Album for American Pie and the second full-length, Sugar.

In between a marathon of touring, they released Head On Straight in 2002. The single “Take Me As I Am” received a GRAMMY®️ Award nomination in the category of “Best Rock Performance by a Duo or Group with Vocal” as the album vied for “Best Rock Album”—only to lose to Bruce Springsteen, “which is still a huge honor being from Jersey,” laughs Dan.

After a five-year hiatus, the three-piece returned to the charts on the heels of Tonic in 2010, landing in the Top 50 of the Billboard Top Rock Albums Chart and Top 25 of the Billboard Top Independent Albums Chart. Following a successful Pledge Music campaign, they re-recorded the seminal Lemon Parade acoustically for 2016’s Lemon Parade Revisited.

“The idea was, ‘How do we do something new?’,” continues Jeff. “We wanted to take it back to the origins of the tracks. So, we sat in a room with acoustic guitars and played. It was a gratifying moment. At the same time, it made us realize that we really enjoy making rock. We love the thrill of playing. It’s come full circle recently, and it’s affected what we’re creating now.”

Outside of Tonic, each musician made a pronounced musical impact of his own. As a sought-after composer for film, television, and video games, Jeff wrote the score for HBO’s critically acclaimed The Night Of in addition to composing for Legion, Counterpart, Star Trek: Discovery, and more. He garnered the 2017 Primetime Emmy®️ Award in the category of “Outstanding Music Composition for a Limited Series, Movie, or Special” for Fargo. Dan played bass in the multiplatinum pop rock outfit The Fray before going on to establish himself as a writer and producer. In recent years, he’s been involved in artist management, working with the likes of Joe Jonas and Adam Lambert. Meanwhile, Emerson ignited a successful solo career, including albums such as Cigarettes and Gasoline [2007], Beauty in Disrepair [2014], and his 2019 third full-length 32 Thousand Days.

No matter what, the members of Tonic find themselves coming back together, hitting the road every year.

“This is like musical home base for us,” Dan leaves off. “From there, we can branch out and do other things, but this is something we all go back to. The fact the three of us have managed to stay together since 1996 with only a few years off is something we’re very proud of. The truth is we’re just three dudes from New Jersey and New York who have the same sensibilities. That’s why we’re still together decades later.”

Jeff agrees, “Every time we get back together, it just sounds and feels like Tonic.”

“The songs keep us around,” smiles Emerson. “We love seeing the excitement in fans’ eyes. We’re all connected. When we play, it’s a moment where we all feel something together.” | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/Tonic%20-%202025%20Approved%20Photo%20%28Resized%29.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Sandy Springs Farmers Market 2025</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-springs-farmers-market-2025</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-springs-farmers-market-2025</guid><description>Shop for fresh produce and artisan foods every Saturday morning at the Sandy Springs Farmers Market. Beginning April 12,  vendors set up shop around the City Green, many bringing their farm to your table. Other vendors offer artisan foods.

Market hours are 8:30 a.m. - NOON.  

﻿Please note: For the Farmers Market event only, dogs are welcome in the plaza and sidewalk areas during Market hours; please remember that pets are not permitted on the Lawn, landscaped beds, or the fountains. | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2022-07/farmersmarket.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Dino Egg Hunt for Kids with Disabilities</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/dino-egg-hunt-kids-disabilities-8</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/dino-egg-hunt-kids-disabilities-8</guid><description>Join us for our fifth annual Dinosaur-themed egg hunt designed to create an opportunity for children with disabilities to have an inclusive experience with their families. When the egg hunting begins, the event will be monitored for safety. There will be an accessible area for children in wheelchairs to score some eggs. Spots are limited to accommodate children that prefer their personal space. Each timeslot includes time to go back to prehistoric times with an educational fossil dig and dino play yard! Your kids will dig for real fossils as we have over 70 different fossils to excavate. Each kid will take home three of their favorite fossils that they find. We also have an assortment of dinosaur statues in our "DINO PLAY YARD" ranging from several of our 2 foot baby dinos, to "Flower" our 8-foot long dino that all kids LOVE to play on and get their photos taken with. The best part is our meet and greet with our Lifesize prehistoric guest!

 Dino egg hunt, fossil dig, dino play yard and photo opportunities make this for a full-on Junior Paleontologist event. Registration required prior to event. Multiple egg hunt sessions available. Spots are limited in each session. We will not be able to accept registration on site.

 Registration time slot is based on the family member with a disability age, register any siblings for that same age group that would like to participate (they will egg hunt together in the same group regardless of age). You do not need to register parents/guardians, just answer how many people will accompany during checkout.

 Recommend coming 15 minutes prior to timeslot to navigate parking and check-in.

 Registration.sandyspringsga.gov

 Plase contact Jane Jarrett at jjarrett@sandyspringsga.gov for accommodation requests.

This event includes custom eggs that have collectable dinosaurs. This service is fulfilled by Canterbury Enterprises Inc. They employ people with disabilities creating opportunities for meaningful work and income.

 WARNING: CHOKING HAZARD Small parts. Not for children under 4 years. | Venue: Morgan Falls Overlook Park </description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/2025%20-%20DinoEggHunt%20-%20Web%20-%20REV%201.00.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Gallery at City Springs - Clay Fisher </title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/gallery-city-springs-clay-fisher</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/gallery-city-springs-clay-fisher</guid><description>This current exhibit features the work of photographer Clay Fisher. 

Clay enjoys photographing a variety of subjects including people, nature, architecture, landscapes, rural areas, and other themes.  His favorite form of photography is nature and travel, which has taken him to several U.S. National Parks, Georgia State Parks Nature Preserves and National Forests. His body of work captures the diversity, complexity and reverence often overlooked by the human eye within these natural places.  

His work has been exhibited at the Georgia State Capitol, galleries, juried exhibitions, various businesses throughout the southeast and published in newspapers and magazines.

Additionally, he serves on the Executive Committee of SlowExposures, an annual photography event hosted in Zebulon Georgia that celebrates the rural south. As a Georgia full-time resident for 30 years, Clay lives in Sandy Springs. 

You can meet the artist and learn more at a reception on Wednesday, April 16 from 6-8 p.m. at the Gallery at City Springs in the lobby of City Hall. | Venue: City Hall</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/Clay%20Fisher%20image%202%20%281%29.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Optimist Club's Easter Egg Hunt</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/optimist-clubs-easter-egg-hunt</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/optimist-clubs-easter-egg-hunt</guid><description>Bring your own basket and get ready to dash through the hunt in search of colorful eggs hidden throughout the field. Keep an eye out for a special surprise visit from the Easter Bunny! Don’t forget your cameras for a chance to snap a photo with everyone’s favorite springtime friend. This is a family-friendly event you won’t want to miss!

Egg hunt for children of various age groups. There will be three different time slots for egg hunts to avoid injury and allowing for all the children to collect as many eggs as they can.

 

Time: 10 am - 12 pm

10:30 am ages 1-3

10:45 ages 4-6

11 am ages 7-9

Rain Date April 26th

Registration: Onsite starting at 10 am for more information visit

https://www.facebook.com/NPOC.org/events | Venue: Hammond Park </description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/Optimist%20Club%20Easter%20Egg%20Hunt%20re-sized.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Astronomy Club - April Event</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/astronomy-club-april-event</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/astronomy-club-april-event</guid><description>The Atlanta Astronomy Club (AAC) is one of the largest organizations of beginner and amateur astronomers in the southeastern United States. The club seeks to provide enjoyment and education to the public through amateur astronomy. Beginners welcomed.


What to learn about the topic of the session? Follow https://www.facebook.com/groups/655263804534791/ | Venue: Lost Corner Preserve</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/Astronomy%20club%20image_1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>City Nature Challenge</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/city-nature-challenge</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/city-nature-challenge</guid><description>City Nature Challenge: April 25th – 28th

This self-guided program allows you to contribute to Citizen Science by documenting local wildlife, plants, and fungi using the iNaturalist app.

Here’s how you can participate: 

1. Download the iNaturalist app Search for iNaturalist in the app store on your smartphone and download it.

Google Play Store 

App Store

2. Learn how to use iNaturalist View helpful video tutorials video tutorials on how to navigate the app and start documenting your observations.

3. Start documenting Take a photo of any wildlife, plants, or fungi you spot! Your phone will automatically geotag and date-stamp your photo to ensure your observation is accurate.

No experience needed! All Citizen Scientists, regardless of age or background, are encouraged to help. Whether you're new to nature observation or a seasoned pro, every observation counts.

If you visit Sandy Springs parks, green spaces, or trails, you can directly help us inventory the diverse plant and animal species in our area. Your contributions will assist scientists and resource managers in creating important biodiversity data.

The best part? You’ll be connecting with the scientific community and helping to advance knowledge of local ecosystems, all while enjoying the outdoors.

We look forward to seeing your observations! | Venue: Online</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/City%20Nature%20Challenge.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>World Tai Chi and Qigong Day</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/world-tai-chi-and-qigong-day</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/world-tai-chi-and-qigong-day</guid><description>We are excited to invite you to celebrate World Tai Chi and Qigong Day on April 26, 2025, at 10 a.m. on the City Green.

This global event promotes health and healing through the ancient practices of Tai Chi and Qigong, and we’re thrilled to be part of this movement encouraging peace and harmony.

Tai Chi is a practice of calm, strength, and balance, and whether you're a seasoned practitioner or new to the practice, this is your chance to experience the transformative power of softness and awareness.

Join us as we come together to move, breathe, and connect to celebrate the art of Tai Chi and share in the global community’s commitment to health and peace.

Event Details:

Date: April 26, 2025

Time: 10 a.m. 

Location: City Green

Hosted by: USA Chen Taiji Center &amp;amp; City of Sandy Springs

Participation: Free for all!

We look forward to having you with us for this special celebration of Tai Chi and Qigong. It’s an opportunity for everyone to experience the benefits of these ancient practices and to connect with others in the spirit of harmony. | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/Tai%20Chi%20on%20the%20City%20Green.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Feathered Friends</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/feathered-friends</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/feathered-friends</guid><description>Wish you had a greater knowledge of the birds that call your backyard home? Spring is a perfect time to learn about all the migratory and full-time feathered friends that live and pass through Sandy Springs. Roseanne Guerra, Master Birder and Birds GA lecturer will share her deep knowledge with us at Lost Corner Preserve. Come for a morning talk in the cottage about all the birds that surround us, followed by a guided walk through the trails of the Preserve where you can put all that newfound knowledge to the test!

Roseanne Guerra is a Master Birder, Naturalist and Environmental Educator who hails from New Orleans and moved to Atlanta in 1988. Her wildlife and education experience includes animal rehabilitation, performing in Zoo Atlanta’s free-flighted bird show and leading many bird walks for Birds GA and numerous nature centers. | Venue: Lost Corner Preserve</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/easternbluebird.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Hoops at Hammond 3v3 Basketball Tournament</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/hoops-hammond-3v3-basketball-tournament</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/hoops-hammond-3v3-basketball-tournament</guid><description>Hoops at Hammond

3v3 Basketball Tournament

Presented by JAM Sports

Saturday, May 3

Register Now!


	Ages 18+
	2 Divisions: Coed Recreational &amp;amp; Coed Intermediate
	4 game guarantee
	All games officiated
	Max roster size: Five players
	Games begin at 11 a.m.
	Hammond Park: 705 Hammond Drive Sandy Springs, GA 30328 | Venue: Hammond Park </description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/Hoops%20at%20Hammond%20_0.png" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Concerts by the Springs: Ansley Stewart Band</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cbts-2025-ansleystewartband</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cbts-2025-ansleystewartband</guid><description>Echoing the halls of the 1960s soul singers with the most powerful gospel depth, combined with the Athens, GA college radio waves of the 1980s, sits an eclectic, thoughtful, and passionate voice that is Ansley Stewart.


	Sunday, May 4 

	
		5:00 p.m. - Heritage Amphitheatre opens
		5:30 p.m. - Food Truck opens. 
		7:00 p.m. - Music begins
	
	
	Reserved table seating may be available. If you reserve a table, be sure to decorate it!
	
		Contact our Box Office: (770) 206-2022 or boxoffice@sandyspringsga.gov 
	
	
	Lawn Seating is FREE and open to everyone. 
	Earplugs will be available at the Concession Stand/Bar tent, free of charge. 


 

Concerts by the Springs 

Concerts by the Springs invites music lovers to enjoy performances at the picturesque Heritage Amphitheatre on Sunday afternoons. Attendees are encouraged to pack a picnic and relax while enjoying the music. 

🎷Getting Here + Know Before You Go  

☀️Summer Concerts in Sandy Springs

 

Ansley Stewart Band



Forever the extrovert, Stewart is most comfortable on stage performing live. Her voice has been said to create life out of thin air (a phenomenon scientists have yet to explain). She emanates her own genre-blending sound that is undeniable upon first listen.

Her original music is written from a place of exploration, trust, and just having some damn fun. She has assembled some of Atlanta’s heavyweights (aka her best buds) to accompany her on the journey:

- Darren Stanley // Drums: Perpetual Groove, Ozone Squeeze, Jimmy Herring, Col. Bruce Hampton

- Nick Johnson // Guitar: Randall Bramblett

- Billy Thornton // Guitar: Ansley Stewart

- Robby Handley // Bass: Lera Lynn, ATL Collective Music Director

Stewart has become a fixture of the Atlanta music scene and has a reputation as one of the most versatile vocalists in town. In addition to pursuing her original music, she is a sought-after session vocalist, guest performer for national touring bands, a prominent member of the ATL Collective family, and dabbles in film and television. | Venue: Heritage Amphitheatre</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/AnsleyStewartBand_1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Sandy Spring Crafting Buddies</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-spring-crafting-buddies-10</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-spring-crafting-buddies-10</guid><description>Bring your current work in progress project, or materials to start a new project and come hang with us! Please feel free to bring any kind of craft (knitting, embroidery, cross stitching, drawing, painting, scrapbooking etc) and spend time working with other creatives!

Sandy Springs Crafting Buddies is free to attend! 

 

Sandy Springs Recreation and Parks inclusive community for people of all ages, abilities and skill sets to come together and share our common thread of passion for crafting. 
Join our Facebook group Sandy Springs Crafting Buddies. | Venue: Barfield Room</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-01/Crafting%20Buddies%20Web%20Asset%203840x2160-%20REV%201.00_2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Sundown Social 2025 </title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/suso</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/suso</guid><description>Sundown Social is back for its third year! Join us for a relaxed, neighborhood gathering with signature cocktails, yard games, and live music. 

LEARN MORE - sundown social | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/2023%20SuSo%20Website%20Asset%203840x2160%20-%20REV%201.00.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Mother Son Dance - Employee Discount</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/mother-son-dance-employee-discount</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/mother-son-dance-employee-discount</guid><description>For the fifth year in a row, the City is offering families a Mother’s Day weekend event to celebrate the very special mom (or mother figure) in our younger residents’ lives. The City’s Recreation and Parks Department’s Mother-Son Dance is scheduled for Saturday, May 10, from 6 - 8 p.m. in the Studio Theater at City Springs. The event will feature dancing, games, snacks, refreshments, and prizes. Each boy will also receive a souvenir photo and a goody bag.

Attire is business casual to semi-formal with a cost of $40 per Mother and Son duo. There is an additional fee of $10 for each additional son. Pre-registration only. Tickets are limited and subject to selling out.

We are excited to announce that our upcoming event is offering a 50% staff discount for those who are flagged as employees in our registration system. Please note the following:


	
	Eligibility: To receive the staff discount, your account must be flagged as an employee. If this is your first time registering with our system and your account has not been flagged, please send an email to recreation@sandyspringsga.gov to have your account flagged.
	
	
	Immediate Family Members: The staff discount also applies to your immediate family members, which include:

	
		
		Spouse
		
		
		Children
		
	
	


We encourage you to take advantage of this great offer and look forward to your participation in the event. If you have any questions, please do not hesitate to reach out to recreation@sandyspringsga.gov | Venue: Studio Theatre</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-01/Mother%20Son%20Dance%20Web%20Asset%20-%20REV%201.00_0.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Mother Son Dance</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/mother-son-dance-8</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/mother-son-dance-8</guid><description>*This ticket is for 1 (one) Mother &amp;amp; 1 (one) K-5th Grade Son. The Mother must register for this ticket. 

*Additional Son Tickets can be purchased as well if needed.

For the fifth year in a row, the City is offering families a Mother’s Day weekend event to celebrate the very special mom (or mother figure) in our younger residents’ lives. The City’s Recreation and Parks Department’s Mother-Son Dance is scheduled for Saturday, May 10, from 6 - 8 p.m. in the Studio Theater at City Springs. The event will feature dancing, games, snacks, refreshments, and prizes. Each boy will also receive a souvenir photo and a goody bag

Attire is business casual to semi-formal with a cost of $40 per Mother and Son duo. There is an additional fee of $10 for each additional son.

To register, please visit the Sandy Springs Recreation and Parks registration site. Pre-registration only. Tickets are limited and subject to selling out.

Scholarships are available by approval at recreation@sandyspringsga.gov

*Please note - this event sells out quickly - tickets are not for sale at the door - purchase tickets in advance* | Venue: Sandy Springs Performing Arts Center</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-01/Mother%20Son%20Dance%20Web%20Asset%20-%20REV%201.00.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>National Kids to Parks Day</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/national-kids-parks-day-1</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/national-kids-parks-day-1</guid><description>Join National Park Trust, Buddy Bison, and kids across America for a fun day of outdoor play at any one of the City's beautiful parks! Sandy Springs along with other cities across the nation are committing to a simple motto: “active kids are healthy kids” and National Kids to Parks Day encourages residents to use local parks and recreation sites to develop more active, healthy lifestyles.

Head to Hammond Park to enjoy food trucks, games, prizes, inflatables, DJ, temporary tattoos, water slides, and more! | Venue: Hammond Park </description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/2023%20Kids%20to%20Parks%20Web%20Asset%20-%20REV%201.00.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Astronomy Club - May meeting</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/astronomy-club-may-meeting</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/astronomy-club-may-meeting</guid><description>The Atlanta Astronomy Club

The Atlanta Astronomy Club (AAC) is one of the largest organizations of beginner and amateur astronomers in the southeastern United States. The club seeks to provide enjoyment and education to the public through amateur astronomy. Beginners welcomed.


What to learn about the topic of the session? Follow https://www.facebook.com/groups/655263804534791/ | Venue: Lost Corner Preserve</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/Astronomy%20club%20image_5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>City Green Live: Face 2 Face </title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cgl-2025-face2face</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cgl-2025-face2face</guid><description>Face 2 Face®️ is an electrifying tribute band that pays homage to two iconic piano legends, Elton John and Billy Joel. Formed in 2010 by Mike Santoro and Ronnie Smith, Face 2 Face captivates audiences nationwide with their exceptional performances and unwavering dedication to bringing the magic of Elton John and Billy Joel's music to life.


	Friday, May 23 

	
		4:00 p.m. - City Green opens 
		6:00 p.m. - Food Trucks open 
		7:30 p.m. - Opener
		8:30 p.m. - Face 2 Face
	
	
	Lawn seating is FREE and open to everyone.
	Reserved table seating may be available. 
	Food Trucks will be on site. 


 

City Green Live 

City Green Live features high-energy, nationally touring artists performing on the City Green, offering attendees a lively, outdoor music experience. 

🎸Getting Here + Know Before You Go

☀️Summer Concerts in Sandy Springs

 

Face 2 Face



Face 2 Face®️ is an electrifying tribute band that pays homage to two iconic piano legends, Elton John and Billy Joel. Formed in Charlotte, North Carolina in 2010 by frontmen Mike Santoro and Ronnie Smith, this talented group of musicians have embarked on a remarkable journey that has captivated audiences nationwide. With their exceptional performances and unwavering dedication, every year they have entertained tens of thousands of people throughout the country.

Bringing the magic of Elton John and Billy Joel's music to life, Face 2 Face®️ recreates the nostalgic experience of witnessing these legendary artists perform live. From Elton John's countless hits and theatrical flair to Billy Joel's heartfelt ballads and piano prowess, the band flawlessly captures the essence of both musicians.

Their captivating stage presence, combined with remarkable attention to detail, has garnered the band a dedicated following. Face 2 Face®️ has earned a reputation for delivering unforgettable shows that transport audiences back to the heyday of these influential artists. Whether performing in intimate venues or commanding large stages, they consistently deliver exhilarating performances that leave fans wanting more.

Over the years, Face 2 Face®️ has become a sought-after act, touring extensively and leaving their mark on numerous cities across the country. Their commitment to authenticity and their passion for the music they perform have earned them accolades and applause wherever they go.

With each show, Face 2 Face®️ reaffirms their commitment to keeping the timeless music of Elton John and Billy Joel alive. Through their dedication, talent, and unwavering love for the craft, they continue to bring joy to the hearts of audiences everywhere, creating a lasting legacy as a premier tribute band in the world of rock and pop music. | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/25%20CGL%20-%20Face%202%20Face%20%28From%20Facebook%205%29.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>The Finale 2025</title><link>https://citysprings.com/events/finale-2025</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://citysprings.com/events/finale-2025</guid><description>The Finale is a show dedicated to highlighting the year-long work of The Performance Division at Elite Studios. It's the culmination of a year’s worth of growth and training for our dancers.


	Show 1 (1:30 p.m.) Little Foundations 3/4 and Little Foundations 5/6
	Show 2 (4:30 p.m.): Foundations 1/2, Elementary Hip Hop, and Boys Hip Hop
	Show 3 (7:30 p.m.): Level 1, Level 2, and Level 3 | Venue: Byers Theatre</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/a15c7b4f-bbc5-42d3-a48b-adb466b5cb72.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Concerts by the Springs: Funk Force Five</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cbts-2025-funkforcefive</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cbts-2025-funkforcefive</guid><description>Playing all of your favorite hits from the 60’s to today, from James Taylor to Taylor Smith, Funk Force Five will get you out of your seat and on to the dance floor with classic and current jams! 


	Sunday, June 1  

	
		5:00 p.m. - Heritage Amphitheatre opens
		5:30 p.m. - Food Truck opens. 
		7:00 p.m. - Music begins
	
	
	Reserved table seating may be available. If you reserve a table, be sure to decorate it!
	
		Contact our Box Office: (770) 206-2022 or boxoffice@sandyspringsga.gov 
	
	
	Lawn Seating is FREE and open to everyone. 
	Earplugs will be available at the Concession Stand/Bar tent, free of charge. 


 

Concerts by the Springs 

Concerts by the Springs invites music lovers to enjoy performances at the picturesque Heritage Amphitheatre on Sunday afternoons. Attendees are encouraged to pack a picnic and relax while enjoying the music. 

🎷Getting Here + Know Before You Go  

☀️Summer Concerts in Sandy Springs

 

Funk Force Five 

Funk Force Five is Atlanta’s Premier Top 40 cover band. Playing all of your favorite hits from the 60’s to today, from James Taylor to Taylor Smith, Funk Force Five will get you out of your seat and on to the dance floor with classic and current jams! From East to West Coast, Funk Force Five has provided the soundtrack for all kinds of people at all kinds of events. Get ready to move your feet with the choreography and sing along with the songs, you’ll be sure to know every one in the setlist. The hits will keep coming all night long! Featuring a professionally trained rhythm section, with some of the baddest players in Atlanta, a horn section that is always ripping, and front line personalities that will draw you in from the first note, Funk Force Five is coming to your town to get down! | Venue: Heritage Amphitheatre</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/Band%20Ben%20foreground%20%28Resized%29.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Sandy Spring Crafting Buddies</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-spring-crafting-buddies-7</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/sandy-spring-crafting-buddies-7</guid><description>Bring your current work in progress project, or materials to start a new project and come hang with us! Please feel free to bring any kind of craft (knitting, embroidery, cross stitching, drawing, painting, scrapbooking etc) and spend time working with other creatives!

Sandy Springs Crafting Buddies is free to attend! 

 

Sandy Springs Recreation and Parks inclusive community for people of all ages, abilities and skill sets to come together and share our common thread of passion for crafting. 
Join our Facebook group Sandy Springs Crafting Buddies. | Venue: Barfield Room</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-01/Crafting%20Buddies%20Web%20Asset%203840x2160-%20REV%201.00_3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Food That Rocks 2025</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/food-rocks-2025</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/food-rocks-2025</guid><description>FOOD THAT ROCKS, a tasting event celebrating Sandy Springs’ diverse restaurant scene for ONE NIGHT ONLY at City Springs.  Patrons will sip, savor, and celebrate the community’s vibrant culinary scene! 

Tickets go on sale April 11. | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-03/foodthatrocks.sandysprings.logo_.toap_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>City Green Live: September in the Park </title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cgl-2025-septemberinthepark</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/cgl-2025-septemberinthepark</guid><description>September in the Park is the ultimate Earth, Wind &amp;amp; Fire and Chicago tribute – celebrating the music of these two iconic groups with a precision unlike any other. Combining the incredible horn arrangements and vocal harmonies that both groups are known for, September in the Park offers a one-of-a-kind entertainment experience!


	Friday, June 13

	
		4:00 p.m. - City Green opens 
		6:00 p.m. - Food Trucks open 
		7:30 p.m. - Opener
		8:30 p.m. - September in the Park 
	
	
	Lawn seating is FREE and open to everyone.
	Reserved table seating may be available. 
	Food Trucks will be on site. 


 

City Green Live 

City Green Live features high-energy, nationally touring artists performing on the City Green, offering attendees a lively, outdoor music experience. 

🎸Getting Here + Know Before You Go

☀️Summer Concerts in Sandy Springs

 

September in the Park | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/25%20CGL%20-%20September%20in%20the%20Park.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Astronomy Club - June meeting</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/astronomy-club-june-meeting</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/astronomy-club-june-meeting</guid><description>The Atlanta Astronomy Club (AAC) is one of the largest organizations of beginner and amateur astronomers in the southeastern United States. The club seeks to provide enjoyment and education to the public through amateur astronomy. Beginners welcomed.


What to learn about the topic of the session? Follow https://www.facebook.com/groups/655263804534791/ | Venue: Lost Corner Preserve</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-02/Astronomy%20club%20image_6.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>ASO: The Music of John Williams</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/aso-music-john-williams</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/events/aso-music-john-williams</guid><description>Relive the adventures of your favorite film characters through the power of a live orchestra performance! The Atlanta Symphony Orchestra fills Byers Theatre with the masterful film music of John Williams, who scored the most compelling moments from Star Wars, Jurassic Park, the Indiana Jones and Harry Potter series, Jaws, Schindler’s List, ET, and more. | Venue: Sandy Springs Performing Arts Center</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2025-01/f77bdf84-eda3-4c3e-afb4-5c2953e62ef6.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item><item><title>Juneteenth Celebration</title><link>https://sandyspringsga.gov/juneteenth</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandyspringsga.gov/juneteenth</guid><description>Save the Date 

Juneteenth, also known as Freedom Day or Emancipation Day, commemorates the emancipation of enslaved African Americans in the United States. Communities across the country celebrate Juneteenth in various ways, reflecting the rich cultural diversity and historical significance of the event.

Celebrate Juneteenth at City Springs! The annual free, family-friendly Juneteenth Celebration in 2025 promises to be an exuberant tribute to freedom and liberty. Attendees can anticipate an extraordinary experience!

More details to come! | Venue: City Green</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://up.sandyspringsga.ddev.site/sites/default/files/2024-03/2024%20Juneteenth%20Website%20Asset%20-%20REV%201.00.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="0"/></item></channel></rss>
